MENU [](https://cyberfear.com/)

* X

**Privacy Policy for CyberFear**
================================

At CyberFear, accessible from https://cyberfear.com, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by CyberFear and how we use it.

If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.

This Privacy Policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in CyberFear. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

**Consent**
-----------

By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms.

**Information we collect**
--------------------------

The personal information that you are asked to provide, and the reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear to you at the point we ask you to provide your personal information.

If you contact us directly, we may receive additional information about you such as your email address, the contents of the message and/or attachments you may send us, and any other information you may choose to provide.

When you register for an Account, we may ask for you to choose a username and a password.

We store the day of user's last login for the purpose of account deletion when it is past due date.

**How we use your information**
-------------------------------

We use the information we collect in various ways, including to:

* Provide, operate, and maintain our webste

**Log Files**
-------------

CyberFear does not log visitors therefore we do not have log files containing visitor's information.

We do not log IP addresses with the exception of registration anti-flood. Upon registration we keep an IP address for exactly 5 minutes during which you cannot register another account from this IP. Once 5 minutes passes, the IP entry is gone. During these 5 minutes the IP entry is not tied to any other information, therefore we cannot tell who this IP belongs to.

**Cookies**
-----------

We use cookies for session identification.

**Advertising Partners Privacy Policies**
-----------------------------------------

CyberFear website does not contain any external tracking scripts or cookies.

**CCPA Privacy Rights (Do Not Sell My Personal Information)**
-------------------------------------------------------------

Under the CCPA, among other rights, California consumers have the right to:

Request that a business that collects a consumer's personal data disclose the categories and specific pieces of personal data that a business has collected about consumers.

Request that a business delete any personal data about the consumer that a business has collected.

Request that a business that sells a consumer's personal data, not sell the consumer's personal data.

If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.

**GDPR Data Protection Rights**
-------------------------------

We would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:

The right to access - You have the right to request copies of your personal data. Keep in mind that except for your hashed username and the day of last login, we do not have any more data to provide.

The right to rectification - You have the right to request that we correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request that we complete the information you believe is incomplete.

The right to erasure - You have the right to request that we erase your personal data, under certain conditions.

The right to restrict processing - You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.

The right to object to processing - You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.

The right to data portability - You have the right to request that we transfer the data that we have collected to another organization, or directly to you, under certain conditions.

If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.

**Children's Information**
--------------------------

Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.

CyberFear does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.
